本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
好了  一切都安排妥了
Okay, it's all set.
这周末我带查莉和泰迪去芝加哥
Charlie, Teddy and I are going to Chicago this weekend.
-拜访下姑奶奶内尔  -内尔姑姑怎么还是个奶奶
-To visit great aunt Nell. -What's so great about aunt Nell?
辈分里带个“奶奶”的  只能说明他们已经很老了
Calling a relative great just means they're really old.
没错吧  奶爸
Right, great dad?
我猜在我接受这个名号后
Well, I guess I deserve <i>that</i>
是不是应该有权利在这里安静的吃我的燕麦粥了
For quietly sitting here eating my oatmeal.
同志们  别瞎说了
You guys, don't be ridiculous.
她并不是因为老才叫奶奶的
She's not great because she's old,
她叫奶奶是因为她很有钱
She's great because she's rich.
如果我们能把她的马屁拍好了
And if we kiss up to her,
我们就会进入她的遗产继承人的行列中
she'll put us in the will.
老妈  我真搞不明白为什么非要让我去
Mom, I don't understand why I have to go
而且男同胞们却可以不去
and the guys don't.
因为  宝贝  那有一大堆钞票在等着我们去争取
Because, honey, there's a lot of cash on the line
所以我要和一支胜利队前往
so I'm going with the "a" team.
恭喜  你是胜利队的一员
Ha ha, you made the "a" team!
等我们走后  你们这些男同胞们去把阁楼清扫干净
And while we're gone, I want you guys to clean out the attic.
噢  听到没  衰人队  胜利队万岁
Oh, take that, "b" team! "a" team rules.
嘿
Hey!
牛什么  你也就只能去芝加哥
Yeah well, you only get to go to Chicago!
我们可以去阁楼
We get to go to the attic.
咱们还不如他们呢
That's not better.
我知道  衰人队丢死人了
I know, "b" team stinks.
听好了  衰人队的同胞们  等女同胞们走后
Listen up, "b" teamers, I've got something.
我也有很重要的事情要去办
Very important to do while the girls are gone,
所以打扫阁楼这事就剩你们哥俩了
So you two are gonna clean out the attic by yourselves.
清理出来的垃圾怎么处理
What are we supposed to do with all that junk?
我们可以来次庭院大甩卖  从中赚一笔
We could have a yard sale, make some money off it.
算了  馊主意
No, that's stupid.
等一下  这是个金点子
Wait a minute. That's a really good idea.
PJ  我觉着这是你人生中的第一个金点子
P.J., I think that's the first good idea you've ever had!
什么  才不是呢  他上次
What? No, it's not. He had the...
你是不是
Didn't you do the...
哇噢  恭喜  零的突破
Wow, congratulations. Well done.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z  杨阳TomMR
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
■
校订： line
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第二季第十三集
Good Luck Charlie  S02E13  Charlie Shakes It Up
呜  难以置信我居然睡过了整个飞行过程
Whoo, I can't believe I slept the entire flight.
是啊  你错过了查莉
Yeah, you missed Charlie's.
那长达两个小时的“一闪一闪小星星”演唱会
Two-hour rendition of "twinkle, twinkle, little star."
-噢  再唱一遍  查莉  -饶了我们吧
-Ohhh, sing it again, Charlie. -No!
噢  看啊
Oh look.
内尔姑姑派车来接我们了  太贴心了
Aunt Nell sent a car for us. Isn't that sweet?
一点儿也不贴心
That's not sweet!
那个老太婆居然浪费我们即将到手的钞票
That old bat's wasting money that could be ours someday.
你听到了吗  查莉
You hear that, Charlie?
你能从中感受到爱吗
Can you feel the love?
嘿  老爸
Hey, dad...
停  停  现在没时间
No no! Not now.
-你看什么呢  -别  呃  老天
-What are you watching? -Don't... aw, man.
电视史上仅有的
<i>Only the greatest show</i>
也是最伟大的电视节目“希金斯与索克”
In the history of television: "Higgins & Zork."
弗兰克·希金斯  一位硬汉派的人类大侦探
Frank Higgins, hardboiled human Detective.
和他的好战外星人搭档索克
And his trigger-happy alien partner Zork!
这俩人穿梭于宇宙中  并肩作战
Together the two of them go through space.
在银河系中  惩恶扬善
And they fight intergalactic crime.
这就是老妈走后
<i>This</i> is the important thing.
你的当务之急
You had to do while mom was gone?
没错
Yes.
听着  当我和你妈结婚后
Look, when your mom and I first got married,
她认为我在看节目上花的时间有点儿多
She thought I spent a little too much time watching the show.
还有出席交流会
And going to conventions.
还有买那很酷的服装
And buying really cool costumes!
但这并不代表我有什么问题
But it's not like I have a problem.
哇  不能把他们俩放在一起
Whoa! Can't have these two together.
他俩是敌对的
That is bad blood.
厉害  你对此管理得还真是井井有条
Yeah, you got it under control.
听好了  我只有七十二小时
Look, I've only got 72 hours.
来看整套的六十四集  你俩到底有何企图
To watch all 64 episodes, so what do you guys want?
赶紧在三十秒之内告诉我
And tell me in 30 seconds or less.
呃  好吧  事情就是我们想
Uh, okay, um, the thing that we want is...
-还剩二十四秒  -你来吧  盖比
-24 seconds. -Take it, Gabe.
我们想往庭院大甩卖的商品上打上价格标签
We want to put prices on all the yard-sale stuff.
-我们有标价枪吗  -没有
-Do we have a pricing gun? -No.
但如果你想见识见识酷到爆的标价枪
But if you want to see a really cool gun,
就看看索克的
Check out Zork's.
不要  索克  停下
No, Zork, stop.
冷静  老兄
<i>Keep your cool, man.</i>
海王星只是一个循规蹈矩的行星
Neptune is a by-the-book planet.
太好看了
This is so good.
哇  这是哪啊
Whoa, what is this place?
为什么司机要把我们带到
Why would the driver take us to a...
-电视摄影棚  -我也不知道
-A tv studio? -I have no idea.
但如果内尔姑姑这么挥霍钱财
But if aunt Nell's on a spending spree,
那我们就要把这苗头扼杀在摇篮里
we've gotta nip this in the bud.
欢迎来到“舞动芝加哥”
Welcome to "shake it up, Chicago."
我是加里·王尔德  而你们一定是传说中的邓肯炫舞姐妹
I'm Gary Wilde and you must be the fabulous Duncan sisters.
-噢  -传说中的谁
-Oh. -The what now?
邓肯炫舞姐妹啊  您今晚要录期节目
The Duncan sisters. You're performing on the show tonight.
这下好玩了  你以为我们是
That's funny. You think that we're...
邓肯炫舞姐妹  他刚已经说了
... Fabulous. He just said so.
我和我的妹妹
My sister and I are.
能上您的节目感到很激动
So excited about performing on your show.
这是唱的哪出戏
What are you doing?
我真的很感谢这位大好人可以让我们登台演出
I'm thanking this wonderful man for putting us on tv.
-这小家伙是谁  -噢  她叫查莉
-And who's this little creature? -Oh, this is Charlie.
她是  呃
She's, um...
邓肯炫舞姐妹中最小的
The youngest Duncan sister.
嗨  我是加里·王尔德  你好啊
Hi, Gary Wilde. How you doing?
有点儿无礼  但我不介意
A little on the rude side, but okay.
总之  我已经迫不急待的想看你们的表演了
Anyway I can't wait to see you guys do your thing tonight.
关于演出  小加  你迫不及待
About that, gar, what is it.
的想看我们演出的什么
You can't wait to see us do.
说的详细点
Exactly?
我的工作人员说你舞技超群
My staff tells me your dancing is amazing.
-你说跳舞  -我们是很牛的舞者
-Dancing? -We're dancers.
地球人都知道
We knew that.
好吧
Okay.
这里有什么地方可以让我私下里
Is there someplace I could have a word in private.
和我的  呃
With my, um...
-姐姐  说几句话吗  -没问题
-Sister? -Sure.
带邓肯炫舞姐妹去她们的化妆室
Show the Duncans to their dressing rooms
都给我伺候好了
and take good care of them.
她们可是咱们节目的大明星
They are the stars of our show.
你听见了吗  我是个大明星
Did you hear that? I'm a star.
噢  嗨  达布尼太太
Oh, hi, Mrs. Dabney.
我来是为了庭院大甩卖的
I'm here for the yard sale.
呃  明天才开始销售
Uh, it's not till tomorrow.
我知道  只要有好东西  我就先下手为强
I know. I like to get a first shot at the good stuff.
我可不希望你们这帮家伙捞到便宜
Not that I expect <i>you</i> people to have good stuff.
那你想买什么
What are you looking for?
任何与猫有关系的
Anything cat-related.
关于猫的书  小猫时钟  小猫图片
Cat books, Cat clocks, Cat pictures,
-小猫的衣服  -成了  成了  我们了解了
-Cat clothes... -Yeah yeah, we got it.
噢  你真幸运  我们这里有个
Oh! Lucky for you we have.
木制猫碗
This genuine wooden Cat bowl.
那个猫碗有啥用
What makes that a Cat bowl?
小猫可以用这个喝水
A Cat could drink out of it.
或者解内急
Or do his business in it.
我就知道我会空手而归
I knew I was wasting my time.
等等  等等  等等
Wait wait wait,
我记得我们还有点什么玩意儿
I think we might have something.
马上回来
Be right back.
近来可好啊
So how you been?
说得跟你很关心似的
Do you really care?
只是想试着度过这段尴尬时刻
Just trying to get through an awkward moment.
我拿来了  一个小猫咪型饼干罐
Here we are. A Kitty Cat cookie jar.
我比较中意这玩意儿
I might be able to take it off your hands.
-开个价吧  -你出多少
-How much you want for it? -Make us an offer.
-你开多少  -你出多少
-You first. -You first.
好了  数到三
Okay, on the count of three,
一起说出你们的心理价位
just say your amounts at the same time.
-一  二  三  -五十美元
-One, two, three. -$50.
十美分
10 cents.
好吧  没关系
Okay, all right.
再试次  请大家这次
Try again. This time, guys,
报价时  稍微贴合实际点儿
Try to be a little more realistic.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
-四十九美元  -十一美分
-$49. -11 cents.
看来我们有得耗了
This could take awhile.
看啊  虽然不及我们平常住的房间大
Well, it's not as big as we're used to,
但还是将就住吧
But it'll do.
-还姐妹  -要说邓肯炫舞姐妹
-Sisters? -The Duncan sisters.
你疯了吗
Have you lost your mind?
泰迪  这是我出现在大荧幕上的绝佳机会
Teddy, this is my chance to be on tv.
老妈  这太疯狂了  咱们还是放弃吧
Mom, this is nuts. We can't do this.
不能放弃  你知道我有多想出现在荧幕中吗
We have to! You know how I've always wanted to be on tv.
还记着我当年参加
Remember when I tried out for that cable show,
（注：山寨美国舞蹈节目《舞魅天下》so you think you can dance）
有线电视节目“快乐假声”吗
"so you think you can yodel"?
记得  实践证明你的假声不快乐
Mm-hmm. And they decided you couldn't.
听着  问题在于我真的很想登台演出
Look, the point is I really want to do this.
这是我的梦想
It's my dream.
我觉着  现在只有一块绊脚石
I mean, there's just one problem.
我们啥舞都不会跳
We don't know any dance routines.
所以呢  咱就找人帮忙呗
So? We'll find someone to help us.
说得轻巧  找谁
Yeah? Like who?
-请进  -嘿  嗨
-Come in. -Hey, hi!
我是洛琪  她是茜茜
I'm Rocky and this is Cece.
我们前来拜访  并欢迎下客串嘉宾
And we like to come by and welcome our guest stars.
没错
Yeah,
同时确认下你们的礼品篮是不是已经安全的送过来了
and make sure your gift baskets have arrived safely.
噢  这有核仁巧克力饼
Oooh, brownies.
这么说来你们就是邓肯炫舞姐妹吗
So you guys are the Duncan... s-sisters?
没错  就是我们
That's right, we are.
我知道你接下来要问什么  不是  我们不是双胞胎
And before you ask, no, we're not twins.
她是不会问的
She wasn't gonna ask that.
这位是查莉  我们的小妹妹
And this is Charlie, our baby sister.
看啊  茜茜  多可爱啊
Aw, Cece, look how cute she is.
我们的母亲一直坚信不论你多年轻  都能大放异彩
Our mother believes you're never too young to absorb the magic.
噢  母亲大人有点神志不清
Oh, mom's kind of a nut log.
你总是嫉妒我们的母亲大人
You've always been jealous of our mom.
好了  我们该撤了  我们一会还要上台跳舞呢
Right, we should get going. We're dancers on the show.
如果你们有什么需要  尽管和我们说
So if there's anything you need, just let us know.
原来你们是舞者  其实
You're dancers? Actually...
呃  我们还真有一事相求
Uh, there is something you could do for us.
是吗  哇
Really? Wow.
之前还没有人这么快就回应我们的
No one's actually ever taken us up on our offer before.
是啊  难道你们就没听说过客套话吗
Yeah, haven't you guys ever heard of an empty gesture?
等一下
Hang on one second.
老爸  你的匹萨到了
Dad, your pizza's here!
等一下  我去拿钱
H-h-h-hang on. I've gotta get some money.
-小猫饼干罐呢  -我们卖给达布尼太太了
-Where's the Kitty Cat cookie jar? -We sold it to Mrs. Dabney.
-什么  -是啊  历时一个半小时
-What?! -Yeah, took an hour and a half,
挣了十块
We made 10 bucks.
同志们  那饼干罐里可放着我们的应急资金
Guys, that cookie jar is where we keep our rainy-day money.
足足五百大洋
There's $500 in that!
哇  那她可赚翻了
Wow, she got a really good deal.
-快给我弄回来  -怎么弄回来
-Go get it back!  How are we supposed to do that?
告诉你吧  那不是我该操心的
You know what? Not my problem.
现在我暂停播放呢  播到要紧的时候啊
Right now I'm in the middle of a two-parter.
正值希金斯和索克回去及时  准备去救波卡洪塔斯
Where Higgins and Zork go back in time to save pocahontas.
谢了
Thank you.
老弟  咱们怎么把饼干罐拿回来
Dude, how are we gonna get the cookie jar back?
我倒希望你能拿出个好主意呢
I was sorta hoping you'd have another good idea.
好吧
Okay.
有了  我想到了  听着
Okay, I got it. All right.
首先咱们先找只会说话的猫
So first we find a talking Cat...
看来你的智慧全用完了
And the well's run dry.
其实我是想你们应该给我们一点
So I was thinking you girlscould give us some input.
-在跳舞方面的技巧什么的  -好的  没问题
-On our dance routine. -Okay, sure.
-就给我们看看你们的舞步行了  -对吖  大姐
-Just show us some of your moves. -Yeah, sis,
让我们看看你懂哪门子舞步
Let's see what you've got.
那个嘛  我乐意之极
Well, I would love to,
不过要抱着查莉来蹦蹦跳跳的
But with Charlie acting up like this,
不说你们也懂的了
Yeah, just...
或者说给我们欣赏一下你们的梦幻舞步之类的
Maybe you should show us some of your dance moves,
那样的话我们就能比较好的融入你们的节目风格啦
That way we can fit into your show's style.
我可不想来这里把自己给搞残废咯
I don't want to come in here and shake it up.
哈哈  我只能说幸好你是个舞者  不是喜剧演员啥的
Ha ha. Good thing you're better dancers than comedians.
对此我深信不疑
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
好吧  我们在"舞动芝加哥"里面大多数都是
Well, most of the numbers we do on
挑嘻哈音乐伴奏的舞蹈
"shake it up, chicago" are hip hop.
好比如说  就像这样  准备好了吗
You know, stuff like this. Ready?
-当时  -就是这样
-Hey. -What?
这玩意我们当然懂
Of course we know that stuff.
不过  能给我们再表演一次嘛
But could you show us one more time?
她们在哪呢  她们在哪呢
Where are they? Where are they?
嗨嗨  你们在这里做啥  小伙子们
Hey hey, guys. What are you doing here?
不好意思  只是这家伙
Sorry, but he wanted to come by and
想来看看邓肯炫舞姐妹
meet the Duncan sisters.
是啊  我还想要她们的亲笔签名
Yeah, I want their autographs.
没问题  和她们说就好了  就在那里
Okay, so ask them. They're right here.
哪儿来着  在这群家伙后面
Where? Behind these guys?
呃  这群家伙就是邓肯炫舞姐妹
Um, these are the Duncan sisters.
我可不这么认为
I don't think so.
不过说实在的  你太秀色可餐了  小妞
But for the record, you are delicious.
呵呵  这趟旅程变得越来越有趣了
Oh, this trip just gets better and better.
呃  弗林  你在胡说些啥呢
Uh, Flynn, what are you talkin'about?
-她们是如假包换的邓肯炫舞姐妹  -看着吧
-Of course these are the Duncans. -Look,
我这里有好多肯花大价钱
I've got people willing to pay big money
去买邓肯炫舞姐妹的亲笔签名照的人呢
for signed pictures of the Duncan sisters.
可惜  此邓肯非彼邓肯
And they ain't them.
她们才是
These are.
-我能够解释  -噢  得了吧
-I can explain that. -Oh, come on!
您老要胡闹到什么时候
When are you gonna just...
其实  我还是愿意听您老来解释
Actually I'd kinda like to hear this myself.
当我们看到这样和我们反差极大的照片时
...And when we saw how different we looked in the pictures,
我们就说"摄影师先生  尝尝炒鱿鱼的味道吧
We said, "mr. Photographer, you are fired.
你压根就没把这事情给做好"
Because you did not do a good job at all!"
好啦  跳舞暂告一段落  大家休息五分钟
Okay, that's enough dancing. Everybody, take five.
好吧  让我来解释一下我家这位大姐
Okay, um, let me explain something about my sister.
第一  她是我母亲大人
First, she's my mother.
第二  她一直梦想着能上一回电视
Second, she's always had this dream of being on tv.
有时候正因为此而做出些疯狂的举动
And it makes her do some crazy things sometimes.
我对你们表示深深的歉意  我们这就收拾东西走人
I'm so sorry. We'll just grab our stuff and go.
-我要和你一起走  -为啥子
-I'd better go with you. -Why?
我愿成为你的护花使者
For protection.
像你这样的美眉走在大街上  没有个肌肉男陪着怎么行呢
A babe like you shouldn't be walking around without some muscle.
拉倒吧  小屁孩  你还不够格呢
Forget it, little dude. You got no shot.
哼  光这样子他是不会死心的
Yeah, like that's gonna stop him.
茜茜  她的妈妈有着我们曾经有过的梦想
Cece, her mom has the same dream we had.
我们应该要帮助她
I mean maybe we should help her.
-那我们有啥好处  -没好处
-What's in it for us? -Well, nothing.
我们只是助人为乐
It's just a nice thing to do.
喔  那之后
Oh! And then after.
他们就会给我们金钱回报啦
They give us money!
不是啦  茜茜  我们这样做是因为我们有一颗仁慈的心
No, Cece, we just do it out of the kindness of our hearts.
好吧  现在我糊涂了
Okay, now I'm just lost.
-我们都不知道他们会不会跳舞  -哪能有多糟
-Look, we don't even know if they can dance. -How bad could they be?
小家伙过来
Come here.
-五六七八  -等等噢
<i>A five, six,</i> <i>seven, eight. </i> <i>Wait a minute.</i>
她们也许不是特别厉害的舞者
The Duncans may not be great dancers,
不过她们做一件事情应该会很成功
But they do have one thing going for them.
那样的话观众们会看不下去的
That people will feel sorry for them.
那样子啊  那就两件事情了
Okay, two things.
-呜呼 -来个绚丽的收场吧  姐妹们
-Whoo! -And big finish, girls.
那个你想拿来和我的饼干罐交换的
So where's this valuable piece of art.
价值连城的艺术品在哪里
You want to trade me for the cookie jar?
就在这里呢  擦亮你的眼睛吧
Here we are. Feast your eyes on this.
-独一无二的哟  -这话倒是不假
-It's an original. -No kidding.
这一看就出自两岁小屁孩的手笔
It was obviously drawn by a two-year-old.
怎么说话的呢  俺都17啦
Hey, I'm 17!
我都不敢相信  你们把我叫过来就是用这东西糊弄我
I can't believe you made me come all the way over here for this!
-先等等啦  -等会等会
-Wait. -Wait, look,
我们只是想要把饼干罐回来
We just want our cookie jar back.
那对我们来说有着很深的感情
It has deep sentimental value to us.
太迟了
Too bad.
现在该到我对它有很深的感情了
Now it has deep sentimental value to me.
你这一个早上大概就对着这罐子过的吧
You must have had quite a morning with it.
那你在罐子里面找到啥东西没
Did you find anything, perhaps, inside the jar?
没  不过我发现有500元用胶带粘在罐盖子那里
No, but I found $500 taped to the lid.
那可是大大的惊喜啊
That was a pleasant surprise.
那你现在愿意做回好人
And now you're going to be a good person.
把罐子给回我们么
And give it back, right?
这可不像是我的风格
That doesn't sound like me.
求求你了  要是我们不拿回来的话  就有大麻烦的
Please. If we don't get it back, we're in big trouble.
这样子啊  除非找点东西来交换
Well, I'm not just gonna <i>gi</i> you the cookie jar back.
-不然我是不会把罐子给回你们的  -要交换啥
-I want something in return. -Like what?
嗯  我想想
Hmm, let's see.
要不请我吃一顿晚饭  看一场表演
How about dinner and a show?
-啥意思  -啊  我的意思就是
-What do you mean? -Well, I mean
我想你们做一顿好吃的晚饭
I want you to cook me a fancy dinner.
再给我表演一下节目  让我开心一下
And dazzle me with an entertaining show.
还有别的选择嘛
Maybe something else?
你们也可以给我来一次舒服的足底按摩
You could give me a nice <i>long</i> foot massage.
还是要晚餐加表演吧
Dinner and a show it is.
好啦  别害羞啦  你们俩快出来啦
All right, come on out, you guys.
哇塞  看起来还不错嘛
Wow, you guys look great.
你们俩都很完美  就是头发没有打上闪光粉
You have everything but glitter in your hair.
要货不  货源充足啊
Want to buy some?
哎呀呀  现在姐姐我可激动了
You guys, this is so exciting!
我觉得是时候把这事情给搞定了
I think that we're actually gonna pull this off.
也许这事要黄了  真正的邓肯炫舞姐妹来了
Or not. Guys, it's the real Duncan sisters.
-噢  不  -噢  太好了
-Oh no. -Oh yes!
是时候赚外快了
Time to make some money!
想当初  我离实现我的梦想仅有一步之遥
I was so close to having my dreams come true.
噢  你刚才那一个半小时所做的
Oh, everything you worked for over the last half hour.
都白忙活了
Is gone.
我们得摆脱她们才行
We have to get rid of them.
嚼绿箭  放轻松啦  小姐们  一切尽在杜斯的掌握之中
Relax, ladies, Deuce has it all under control.
那个  当他说这句话的时候
So when he says he has it all under control,
我们应该感到如释重负呢  还是忧心忡忡
Should we be relieved or worried?
说的对
Yes!
请这边走  这就是你们的更衣室
Over here, and this is your dressing room.
女士优先  请进请进
After you. Ladies first.
做啥子呢
<i>Hey!</i>
反正你们在里面也闲的无聊
As long as you have some time on your hands...
签上你们的大名  注明是给弗林的哟
Make it out to Flynn. That's a "fly"
就是"佛"字不要单人旁  再加两个"木"
Followed by a "nn-nn"!
请坐请坐  这是房子里最好的桌子了
Here you go, best table in the house.
如果你想拥有的话  明天出售哦  亲
And if you like it, it's for sale tomorrow.
晚上好  这是我们今晚的主菜
Bon soir. For our main course this evening,
这是来自大厨独一无二的创意
Ze chef has prepared his own unique creation.
现在为您呈上
Voila.
就热狗啊
A hot dog?
这就是你的晚餐创意
That's your idea of a dinner?
待会还可以看到我们的极富创意的表演哦  亲
Wait till you see our idea of a show.
乡亲们  晚上好呐
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
感谢你们如此安静
And thank you for that quiet,
但是心底里热流涌动的欢迎
But passionate welcome.
开玩笑的时候再打好不  亲
Only on the jokes, hon.
有人从乡下来的不
So anybody here from out of town?
我正要指你啊
I'll just point to you.
-一点都不好笑  -我想我们准备要失去唯一的观众了
-Not laughing yet. -I think we're losing her.
是时候出大招了
Time for the big number.
扬基  杜多  战斗吧  扬基  杜多  公子哥
Yankee doodle keep it up, yankee doodle dandy?
(注解:这是《Yankee Doodle》)
听着音乐和着脚步同姑娘
Mind the music and the step and with the girls?
跳舞
Be handy!?
我看腻了
I've seen enough.
我们已经做到最好了  饼干罐能还给我们不
We did our part, so where's the cookie jar?
你们没开玩笑吧  这表演5块钱都不值  更别说500了
Are you kidding? That wasn't worth $5, never mind $500.
-那你还想我们做点啥  -这个嘛
-What else do you want? -Well,
是时候按摩一下我的脚啦
Guess it's foot-rubbing time.
嘿  你们一人还能分一只脚呢
Oh look, there's one for each of you.
-老爸  你还好吧  -说实话
-Dad, are you okay? -Honestly?
我都觉得自己快要崩溃了
I'm a wreck.
我竟然完全忘记了第22集的时候
I completely forgot about the emotional power.
索克遇见了他那个半人类兄弟
Of episode 22 where...
那时候  表演得太淋漓尽致了
Zork meets his half-human brother.
索克
Zork?!
你在看那部有史以来最好的电视剧
Are you watching "higgins & Zork,"
"希金斯与索克"吗
The greatest tv show of all time?
你也是索克粉
Are you a zorkie?
啊哈  你也是
Look! You are!
我那里有全部64集呢  就在地下室
I've got all 64 episodes downstairs!
如果你想看完的话
And if you want to see them,
把饼干罐给回我们就行了
all it will cost you is one Kitty Cat cookie jar.
-成交成交  -老爸  你还行不行啊
-Deal! -Is it okay with you, dad?
-索克讨厌金星人不 -啊哈哈哈
-Does Zork hate venusians? -Ahhhhh!
嗨  大家看好喽  现在你们有眼福啦
Hey, everybody, and now a real treat!
这是"舞动芝加哥"的舞者们和特邀嘉宾一起带来的表演
The "shake it up, chicago" dancers with special guests.
她们就是  邓肯炫舞姐妹
The Duncan sisters!
大家都动起来
<i>Get on your feet</i><i>right now</i>
挣脱
<i>Break out</i>
你知道我穿囚服很有型
<i>You know I look good</i><i>in stripes</i>
快来给我和我的囚号拍张照
<i>Take my picture</i><i>with my number</i>
我已精疲力尽  真的很扫兴
<i>I tried, but this</i><i>ain't the time</i>
我快撑不住了
<i>I can't stand it</i><i>any longer</i>
噢  宝贝  我要挣脱这束缚
<i>Oooh, baby,</i><i>I've got to break out</i>
<i>Oooh, baby, I've got</i><i>to break out</i>
越狱  一次幸福的逃脱
<i>Jailbreak, sweet escape</i>
摧毁层层围墙
<i>Let's bust</i> <i>the walls down</i>
越狱  一次幸福的逃脱
<i>Jailbreak, sweet escape</i>
马上行动
<i>Get off the ground</i>
监狱也困不住我
<i>Jails can't hold me</i>
倒数三二一  冲出那道门
<i>In two-three-four</i><i>I'll be out the door</i>
挣脱
<i>Break out!</i>
我要挣脱  挣脱
<i>Got to break out,</i><i>break out!</i>
我要挣脱  轻声慢步
<i>Got to break out,</i><i>tiptoe slowly</i>
狱警喊站住  我将应声倒地
<i>When they call "lights out"</i><i>I'll hit the floor</i>
挣脱  我要挣脱
<i>Break out,</i><i>got to break out</i>
<i>Break out, got to</i><i>break out</i>
抓不到我  因为我不走寻常路
<i>Can't catch me</i><i>'cause I'm cool</i>
挣脱
<i>Break out!</i>
监狱也困不住我
<i>Jails can't hold me</i>
倒数三二一  我将冲出那道门
<i>In two-three-four,</i><i>I'll be out the door</i>
挣脱  我要挣脱
<i>Break out,</i><i>got to break out</i>
<i>Break out, got to</i><i>break out</i>
挣脱
<i>Break out!</i>
哇塞  我不得不承认  这感觉实在太棒了
Oh, I gotta admit that was pretty cool.
我也这么觉得  他们好喜欢我们呢
I know. They love me.
广告之后  马上回来
We'll be right back after this.
你们做得很不错哟
That was awesome, you guys.
下周我们还有空
We're available next week.
下下周也是
And the week after that.
是啊  不过现在没空了
Yeah, but not right now.
欧麦雷迪嘎嘎  我们得撤了
Oh goodness. We gotta go.
好吧  芝加哥  我们有缘再见啦
Okay, goodbye, Chicago!
走啦  小家伙
Here, let's go.
祝你好运哟  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie!
查莉吖
Well, Charlie,
芝加哥之行  有好有坏
Chicago was good and bad.
妈妈终于能上一回电视了
Mom finally got on tv...
这是好事
Good.
妮尔阿姨把遗嘱改了
Aunt Nell changing her will.
决定把她的遗产留着她的宠物  雪纳瑞狗米斯
To leave all her money to pet schnauzer mitzi...
这是坏事
Bad.
对我来说  回到家  一切都好
Um, as for me, I'm just glad to be back home.
这里至少一切都回归正轨了
Where everything's normal.
你在看啥呢
What are you looking at?
我不知道
I don't know.
我是指挥官托拉
I am commander toura.
啥帮助也没啊
Not helping.
好吧  那就把这当做是这房子里面一件平常不过的事情吧
Well, that's just about as normal as it gets around this house.
祝你好运咯  小查莉
So good luck, Charlie.
你从芝加哥给我带回来什么啦
So did you bring me anything from Chicago?
啊  这个啊  我都忘记了
Oh yeah, I didn't forget about you.
-迫不及待想看了  -嗨嗨
-Wait until you see what I... -Hey!
你给我带回来俩妞
You got me girls?
不是  本来是一件T恤的啦
No, I got you a t-shirt!
你们在这里做啥呢
What are you guys doing in there?
-我们很想来看看丹佛的景色  -是啊  还真的蛮不错的
-We really wanted to see Denver. -Yeah, it's really nice.
-嗯  我很高兴你们能喜欢  -做啥呀
-Oh, I'm glad you liked it. -What?
不要嘛
No, wait!
也许是放在我的随身箱子里
Maybe I put it in my carry-on.
吓死我了
Oh!
想我了不  小甜心
Hey, babe, miss me?
-别指望了  -说啥呢
-No. -What?
这样子的话  如果杜斯从我钱包里面钻出来
Okay, if that Deuce kid comes out of my purse,
-我就要叫出来了  -那我还是呆在里面好了
-I'm gonna scream. -<i>Well I'll just stay in here.</i>
哟呵  还有薄荷糖呢
<i>Ooh, mints!</i>